That statue kicks ass.
Yeah. yeah.
What kind of pants are those?
They're yoga pants. dumbass.
Everybody knows that.
Well. that statue sure looks
good in those yoga pants.
It sure does.
Yoga pants.
Mm.
Um. Butt-Head?
I wonder if I would look sexy
in yoga pants.
Yeah.
Everyone looks sexy
in yoga pants.
Yeah. except for you. Beavis.
'cause you're disgusting.
No way. Butt-Head.
You heard what she said.
I'm gonna listen to a chick
and not you.
I'm gonna go get
some yoga pants.
and then I shall score.
You've seen it before.
but not on this scale.
I thought we all needed
cheering up. myself included.
So I know how you love
a little bit of rock cooking.
I thought I'd go OTT with it.
You know... you know.
Butt-Head. um.
sometimes I worry that
I'll never score. you know?
But. um...
But this guy will never score.
Yeah. I don't see how he could.
Is this the outback
or something?
He's in the outback
'cause his wife kicked him out.
and now he's living out back
behind his mom's house.
"Mom. can I play breakfast
in the backyard again?"
This guy's survival skill.
is it. like. if he runs out
of food. he just goes
to his mom's house
and gets a bunch
of stuff out of the fridge?
And then he just goes
into the backyard
and cooks it all. yeah.
On one of those tiles
from the roof. yeah.
Why didn't he just. like.
get some Froot Loops
or something?
This breakfast
is a cry for help.
He made a face
out of eggs and sausage
'cause he's lonely.
"Let's make some
pancake boobs here."
He's like. "I'm cooking for two
"in case Jennifer comes back.
Has anyone seen her?
No?
Well. that means more for me."
This is turning out
to be a great day
without Jennifer.
and many more to come. yeah.
"Yeah. my ex-wife likes oranges.
so I guess I'll make her
some orange juice.
And I'll make it here
in her sawed-off leg bone.
That was lovely.
Yup. all good things
must come to an end.
like this filthy breakfast
and my marriage of 14 months.
Come on. Butt-Head.
This is getting too sad.
Yeah.
"And now I filled
this backpack with rocks.
and I'm just gonna go
walk into the ocean."
Yeah.
"In the next episode. you'll
be seeing an outback funeral."
"Let me know if she's there."
"She'll probably cry.
and then she'll regret
running off
with her college roommate."
Yeah.
She'll be like. "You know.
if I hadn't left him.
"he'd still be alive and
cooking me a filthy breakfast
on a rock."
"And don't forget.
if you like this video.
can you please go
find my wife?"
Just smash
that find-my-wife button.
Go get me some yoga pants.
Ooh. yeah.
Uh. here you go. Beavis.
Um. those look kind of small.
Butt-Head.
Of course they look small. dumbass.
That's because they. like.
stretch and stuff so that
they can. like. rearrange
your butt or something.
Oh. yeah. yeah.
That makes sense. yeah.
This is gonna be cool.
Okay.
I'll take these off.
Here we go.
Ah.
Hey. how's it going?
Hey. Butt-Head.
I'm. like. naked in a place
that. like.
chicks have been naked in.
Cool.
Boing. oing. oing.
Okay. okay.
Put these bad boys on.
About halfway there.
Son of a bitch!
Okay.
Here we go.
How do I look?
Uh. Beavis?
Pretty sexy.
Yeah. I'd tap that.
Yeah... ooh.
Uh. Beavis. it looks like
you don't have any nads.
What?
What're you talking about?
Or a schlong.
No way. Butt-Head.
My schlong is right...
No. what happened to my nads?
I know they're in there
'cause these pants
are really making 'em hurt.
Uh. you better take 'em off
before any chicks see you. Beavis.
That's embarrassing.
They won't come off. Butt-Head.
My wiener's going numb.
Just get ahold of yourself. Beavis.
Hold of yourself.
I can't get 'em off.
Ahh!
You gotta help me. Butt-Head.
These pants are cutting off
oxygen to my schlong.
Hmm. we need to find a place
that sells schlong oxygen.
No. we gotta find something
to get 'em off
before my wiener dies.
Damn it.
We just need to.
like. oil 'em up.
and then they'll
just slide right off.
Now just wait over there.
I'll be right back.
Care to try our new
olive oils from Tuscany?
Okay. Beavis.
I got you some oil.
and it has Tuscany in it.
What's that?
I don't know.
but it'll grease you up good.
Open up your pants.
It's not working. Butt-Head.
That's 'cause you need
some muscle. dumbass.
Hold on to that thing.
and let a real man do this.
Uh. Butt-Head. Butt-Head.
Butt-Head. I'm starting to slip.
Hold on. dumbass.
- I can't.
- Almost got it.
No. Butt-Head.
No. no. no... oh. no!
Ahh!
That was cool.
I can't get up. Butt-Head.
Ow. ah.
It just keeps going down.
Uh. don't worry. Beavis.
I'm gonna go get help.
Ow.
Going down.
Oh. yeah.
Eh. but really. Butt-Head.
come on.
Ah. ow. ah.
Uh. excuse me.
We need help and stuff.
What's the problem?
Uh. my friend has no nads.
Ah. ow. ah. ow. ah!
Uh. he says he doesn't know
how to help you. Beavis.
Damn it.
Well. I'll see you at home.
Let me know how it turns out.
Okay. see you later.
Damn it.
Ah. ow.
Ah!
Damn it.
- Good morning.
Chirp.